togetherweserved.com 2019-03-17

# TogetherWeServed Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
TogetherWeServed.com Inc.  
October 1, 2018

TogetherWeServed Inc. (TWS) is committed to protecting the privacy of all TWS Members, as well as all visitors to this Website (the “site”). The following is the TWS privacy statement outlining our policies governing the collection and use of personal information, including registered Member information. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact us at [info@togetherweserved.com](mailto:info@togetherweserved.com)

**Information Collection & Use**

TWS requires Members to register for TWS Membership and provide personal information including but not limited to the Member's name, postal address, phone number and email address. TWS does not collect such information from others. TWS uses this information to establish and deliver the benefits of Membership and to communicate with the Member about new offerings or potential Member benefits.

The collection and use of personal data (along with other kinds of data) is critical to the successful operation of TWS. We collect and use personal data from or about you to support and serve our membership, including to: 

  * Deliver the information, programs, products and/or services you request;
  * Evaluate and respond to your inquiries and submissions;
  * Provide you with customer support and Membership benefits;
  * Communicate with you through various channels, including postal mail, email, telephone, apps, online chats, in person, and social media;
  * Process your payments and account adjustments;
  * Create and manage your Membership registration;
  * Customize your experiences and identify you online, including by displaying offers and advertising tailored to your interests;
  * Evaluate and improve our services, Memberships, benefits, digital services, and other operations (e.g., developing and analyzing new or revised services; performing market research and data analytics; creating and applying data models; and assessing the effectiveness of our websites, apps, communications, advertising, and marketing programs);
  * Comply with and enforce applicable legal obligations, our policies, and our terms and conditions.

TWS may employ companies and people to perform tasks on its behalf or as licensed or formally arranged service providers, and will need to share personal information with these agents to establish and deliver services, information, and other benefits of Membership. TWS's agents do not receive any right to use personal information beyond what is necessary to perform these tasks. TWS will not disclose registration information to third parties, including, but not limited to, companies affiliated with TWS, without your consent or as otherwise stated in this privacy policy. If at some point TWS sells all or a portion of its assets, customer information is one of those assets that would be transferred or acquired by a third party; the third party would then have the right to continue using the personal information as set forth in this policy. TWS may release or exchange personal information if required to do so to comply with applicable law or to enforce its rights or agreements or prevent fraud or reduce credit risk.

TWS also collects and analyze information regarding the use of TWS's Memberships and TWS site activity (“personally identifiable information” or “PII”). PII collected may include but is not limited to web site traffic volume, frequency of visits, type and time of transactions, type of browser and operating system, etc. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, administer the site, and improve the quality and types of Membership delivered. TWS may also collect, track and analyze information that does not personally identify a user in aggregate form. This aggregate data will be used at TWS's discretion and may be shared with third parties. TWS also occasionally shares personal data with select, unaffiliated organizations for use in their own social or Veterans-related missions.

We may collect personal data about you from unaffiliated sources with whom we contract, such as other service providers and data aggregators, as well as from public sources or databases. We may obtain data such as your name, postal address, telephone number, demographic data (such as age, gender, income level, and purchasing profiles), and publicly observed data (such as activity on blogs, videos, and other online postings). We generally use such data to identify potential members or other individuals we try to reach as part of our services, to update personal data we already have about current Members and other individuals (such as an address update), or to enhance our data models.

We may also purchase or license personal data lists from unaffiliated sources and provide access to those lists to other entities.  Although we may enhance such lists by applying our data models, we do not contribute personal data related to TWS members to such lists.

Registered Members will be using the TWS site to view information supplied by other Members. TWS will not review, share, distribute or reference such information except as may be required in providing the requested TWS Membership service, or as provided in the TWS Terms of Use Agreement, or as may be required by law.

**Security**

TWS has implemented processes designed to protect PII and Member information and maintain security. Each registered Member is assigned a unique user name and password which is required to access their account and relationship information. It is the Member's responsibility to protect the security of their login information. TWS's servers are located in secure server environments. Firewalls and other advanced security technologies are employed to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of data.

**Communications**

From time to time TWS requires to communicate with its Membership for various purposes including, but not limited to, the sending of password reminders, membership updates, official newsletters. Members may opt out of receiving selected communications from their account settings.

**Third-Party Advertising Partners**

We may allow third-party service providers to serve advertisements (banners or links), on partner companies behalf, across the Internet.

These advertising service providers may collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our website and associated interactions. Such non-identifiable information does not include your name, address, email address or other personal information. The information is collected through the use of cookies and pixel tags (also known as action tags), which is industry-standard technology used by most major websites.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices for not having this information used by third-party service providers, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Third Party Sites**

TWS's sites may contain links to third party web sites not associated with TWS. TWS is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such sites. Members will need to review the policy statements of these sites to understand their privacy policies.

**_How We Share Personal Data_**

Except as described below, we do not share your personal data with unaffiliated without your consent. You may limit certain sharing of your personal data as described below in Your Personal Data Choices.

  * **Approved Vendors.**  We may share personal data with unaffiliated companies or individuals we hire to provide services or perform business functions on our behalf (such as print, mail, or email vendors; web hosting vendors; cloud service providers; consultants; digital advertising and analytics vendors) because these vendors need access to the personal data to perform the functions we’ve requested of them. These vendors are contractually required to treat the personal data we provide as confidential, and to use the personal data only to provide the services we have requested they perform on our behalf.

  * **Payment Processors.**  We may share your personal data with banks or other entities that process payment transactions or provide other financial services, and for fraud prevention and credit risk reduction purposes.

  * **Select Organizations.**  We may occasionally share personal data, or engage in “list exchanges,” with select organizations when we believe such data sharing is in the best interest of our Members.

  * **Social Media Advertising Networks.**  We may share personal data with social media networks to facilitate their delivery of our customized advertising or messages on their network. The limited personal data we provide as part of the networks’ custom audience programs (generally email addresses) facilitates the delivery of our content to the right social media user. These networks only use the personal data we provide to identify you for these purposes. The delivery of customized social media ads or other content, and your ability to opt-out, is governed by the privacy policies of the social media companies, not this Privacy Policy.

TWS may also share your personal data with other third parties as follows:

  * **Pursuant to Legal Requirements.**  We may disclose your personal data (1) if we believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or legal process, such as in response to a court order, subpoena, or similar investigative demand; (2) as we deem appropriate or necessary in response to requests for cooperation from a law enforcement agency, taxation authority, or other government agency; and (3) to defend against legal claims, exercise our legal rights, or as otherwise required by law.

  * **To Protect Ourselves, Our Members, or Others.**  We may disclose your personal data when we believe disclosure is necessary (1) to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud, or other wrongdoing; (2) to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company, our Members, our employees, our websites and apps users, or others; and (3) to enforce our terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.

**Choices in Data Collection and Use**

**_Personal Data Access_**  
If you wish to review and/or request changes to certain personal data we have collected about you (such as your current contact information, username and password), you may do so by logging into your TWS account or by contacting us as identified above. In some cases, you may also have a right to (i) request deletion of certain personal data or (ii) obtain a copy of such data in an accessible format. We will make reasonable attempts to comply with such requests where applicable, but may refuse requests where we are otherwise legally required to retain the data, or the requests are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, risk the privacy of others, or are impractical.

**_Personal Data Sharing_**  
If you would like to request that we no longer share personal data with Service Providers and/or unaffiliated organizations, you may do so by completing our Privacy Opt-Out Form or by contacting us as identified below. If you make such a request, it will not prevent such third-parties from using any personal data we shared with them prior to completing the opt-out process, or any data they have collected directly from you or others.

  **_TWS Communications_**  
You may choose to opt-out of some or all future communications (mail, email, phone) from TWS. You can do so by completing our Privacy Opt-Out Form or by contacting us as identified below. For email, you can also opt-out by clicking on the “unsubscribe” links in the footer of our emails. (Please note that when opting-out of emails, you may still receive “transactional” emails, which contain information you specifically request or information related to your Membership purchase or renewal.) For phone or text messages, you can also opt-out by following the contact instructions we provide in the phone call or replying “STOP” to any text message to which you’ve previously consented.  We will honor your opt-out requests as soon as practical and as required by applicable law.

  **_Cookies_**  
Most web browsers can be set to reject cookies or provide notice when cookies are placed on your device. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Although it is up to you whether to accept cookies from our websites, if you reject cookies, certain functions on our Site may not work properly, and your ability to use some areas of the sites may be limited. It is also important to note that some opt-out mechanisms generally rely on cookies to retain your opt-out preferences. So if you reject or erase cookies, your opt-out choices may not function properly.

We strive to provide you reasonable choices regarding our collection, use, and sharing of your personal data. We provide you access to review and correct your personal data, provide you options regarding how we share personal data, and provide you control over how we communicate with you, among other choices.  You may contact us at any time regarding these choices as follows:

  * Email us at admin@togetherweserved.com
  * Call us at 888) 398-3262
  * Write to us at Togetherweserved.com Inc., 9430 Topanga Canyon Blvd., Ste 203, Chatsworth, CA 91311

**_Links to Other Websites_**

Our websites and apps may provide links or automatically redirect you to third-party websites that are not controlled by TWS or governed by this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement or a link for a Member benefit offered by a third-party, you may be redirected to a website operated by that party. These third-party websites may collect personal data and other data from or about you. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any website that we do not control, and your interactions with such websites are governed solely by the privacy policies of the entity operating the websites, not this Privacy Policy.

**_Social Media_**

If you are logged in to your social media account or use your social media credentials to log-in to our websites or apps, and if you use a “like” button or similar social media feature on our website or app, those social media companies may collect certain information about you, such as your IP address and which pages you visit on our websites or apps. These social media features are not operated by TWS. Your interactions with social media companies and the use of their features are governed by the privacy policies of the social media companies that provide those features, not this Privacy Policy.

**_United States-Based Organization_**

TWS is headquartered in the United States and all of our data processing activities occur in the United States. Any personal data you provide to us, including through our websites and apps, will be transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States. By providing us your personal data or using our websites and apps, you acknowledge that the United States has standards for the processing and storage of personal data that may not be equivalent to (and may be less comprehensive than) those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen, and you consent to our collection, transfer, processing, and storage of your personal data in the United States.

**_Children/COPPA_**

Our websites and apps are not intended for use by children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal data from such children. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal data, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us so that the personal data can be deleted.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

TogetherWeServed.com Inc. reserves the right to make changes to this privacy statement. Any changes to this statement will be posted online and accessible via the TWS user portal 30 days prior to taking effect.

**Togetherweserved.com Inc.**
